Guide to the Stanford University Postcard Collection
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Postcards (individual)
  - Eating Clubs, interior courtyard, 1917 pm; 140; Sepia Print
    Message: Dearr Mother, We received the box this afternoon. Olga was just needing the things. Aunt Lucy says to thank you for the band. We haven't said anything about going home yet but I want to come Sunday. We just went shopping in Palo Alto. Spent seventy cents. Love to you and Dad, Esther. to Mrs. E. E. Cleese
    Imprint: Souvenir Publishing Company
    same image as #139
  - Encina Gym, exterior, 141; B/W Print
    Encina Gym (2nd)
  - Encina Hall, exterior view (front & west wing), post 1906; 142; Sepia Print
    Caption: 1907 - Encina Hall, Stanford University, Calfornia
    no chimneys
    Encina Hall
  - Encina Hall, exterior view (front & west wing), post 1906; 143; B/W Print
    no chimneys; caption is partially cut off; same image as #142
  - Encina Hall, exterior view (front & west wing), post 1906; 144; Tinted Print
    same image as #142
  - Encina Hall, front view, post 1906; 145; Sepia Print
  - Encina Hall, front view from the NW, post 1906; 146; Sepia Print
    no chimneys, palm trees and roses in foreground
  - Encina Hall, front view from the NW, post 1906; 147; Sepia Print
    same as #146 but lacking an imprint
  - Encina Hall at night with students on steps, post 1906; 148; Photo
    taking of the night shirt parade photo?
  - Encina, front view, 1907 pm; 149; B/W Print
    Caption: Encina Hall, Stanford University, Cal.
    Message: It was the hardest fought game I ever saw. The teams were very evenly matched but we got 21-11. Wasn't that fine. I'll write more later. to Charles W. Thomas
    Imprint: L.O. Knopf Co.
    still has chimneys
  - Encina, distant view, 1913; 150; Sepia Print
    Message: in ink on back: May 7, 1913 8:15 a.m.
  - Encina, front view, post 1906; 151; Sepia Print
  - Encina, distant view, post 1906; 152; Sepia Print
  - Encina, front view, post 1906; 153; Sepia Print
  - Encina, front view, 1912 pm; 154; Sepia Print
    Caption: Encina Hall, Stanford, University, Cal. 1843
    Message: Dear Alden This is here you will live when you come to Stanford. Suppose your school commences soon. Love, Olive. to Alden Johnson
  - Encina, front view, pre 1906; 155; Color Print
    Caption: 862 - Encina Hall, Stanford University, California
  - Encina, front view, 1908 pm; 156; Tinted Print
    Message: Dear Gertie, I guess you have heard from babe she is in Capitola with Henderson may be away two weeks dad got home last night. Gladys L. is home and her baby is very sick. to Gertie Riehl
    image is probably pre-06: still has chimneys
  - Encina, front view, 1914 pm; 157; Color Print
    Message: Hello Pete. Guess you're going to school by now. This is where I live. Haven't been hazed by the Sophs lately. Think my vacination is going to "take" & may have to drop foot-ball. Don't like this style as well as American anyway. Well, you folks let me hear from you some day. Bill to Wilford Allen Jr.
  - Encina walkway from the Quad, Undated; 158; Sepia Print
    Caption: verso: Encina Walk
  - Engineering buildings and Geology corner, 1911 pm; 159; Sepia Print
    Caption: Geology and Engineering Buildings, Stanford
    Message: Roble Hall, Oct. 25, 1911. Dear Henriette - I am having such a good time I don't know whether I will want to go home or not.... Had a walk around Dr. Jordan's house today. The girls are expecting you for the rally. Love to all, Auntie. to Henriette Thomas
    Engineering Buildings
  - Engineering buildings and Engineering corner, post 1907; 160; Sepia Print
    Caption: 1904 Engineering Buildings, Stanford University, California
  - Entrance gates, viewed from Palo Alto side, pre 1906; 161; Sepia Print
    Entrance Gates (2nd)
  - Entrance gates, viewed from arboretum, pre 1906; 162; Photo
    possibly a B/W Print
  - Entrance gates, oblique angle from arboretum, 1906 pm; 163; B/W Print
    Caption: Entrance to grounds, Stanford University, Cal.
    Message: Yes - I did hear about it, but had not seen the notice in the paper. Mr. H won a fine wife & somebody else escaped getting a fine wife. When are you going to follow H's example? Regards, T. E. Robinson to Frank Peters
  - Entrance gates, oblique angle from arboretum, pre 1906; 164; B/W Print
    Caption: Entrance to Stanford University, Cal
    Imprint: E.C. Kropp
    same vantage point as #163
  - Entrance gates, oblique angle from arboretum, 1908 pm; 165; B/W Print
    Caption: Entrance to Stanford Campus
    Message: I should judge people are some siwer then they exit thru this than when they entered - they ought to be. E.O. to Hulda Kruslock
    Imprint: Fritz Muller
  - Entrance gates, oblique angle from arboretum, pre 1906; 166; Sepia Print
    same image as #165
  - Entrance gates, oblique angle from arboretum, pre 1906; 167
    Caption: Entrance gate Stanford University, Cal.
  - Entrance gates, oblique angle from arboretum, pre 1906; 168; B/W Print
    Caption: Entrance to Stanford University, California
    Imprint: Edward H. Mitchell #6070
    image as yellowish overtones
  - Entrance gates, oblique angle from arboretum, pre 1906; 169; Color Print
    Caption: Entrance to Stanford University Grounds, California
    Imprint: Edward H. Mitchell #402
    same image as # 168
  - Entrance gates oblique angle from Palo Alto side, pre 1906; 170; Color Print
    Caption: Main Entrance, Stanford University
    has white space on front for messages
  - Entrance gates, oblique angle from Palo Alto side; with image of collapsed gate after the earthquake, 1906; 171; Tinted Print
    Message: Wed am. May 30/06. Dear Ruth: Think I will be home Friday. Am living "The Strenuous Life." Hope you are better. All is O.K. now I guess. Be a good little girl. De
    Pre-06 image is color; post -06 image is BW
  - Entrance gates, from arboretum, pre 1906; 172; Color Print
    Caption: 183 Palo Alto, California. Entrans to the Stanford University
    Imprint: Charles Weidner
  - Faculty houses of Prof. W. F. Durand and H. J. Ryan, Undated; 173; Sepia Print
    Faculty Residences
  - Faculty houses, Undated; 174; Sepia Print
    probably a different view of same houses in no. 173
  - Residence of Prof. J. O. Griffin, 1910; 175; Photo
    Caption: Stanford University Home of Prof. J. O. Griffin
    Message: A few California roses for your Easter - hoping this finds you all well and enjoying your life in Germany. with greetings from the Griffins. Stanford March 7 -10
  - Residence of Prof. J. O. Griffin, Undated; 176; Photo
    Caption: Home of Prof. Griffin Stanford University
    Message: A merry Christmas & a happy New Year to you and yours Bessie H. Griffin
    name Griffin inked out on front; 553 Salvatierra written on UL corner
  - Alpha Tau Omega - exterior of house, Undated; 177; Sepia Print
    fraternities
  - Beta Theta Pi - exterior of house, Undated; 178; Photo
    Caption: Beta Theta Pi
  - Beta Theta Pi - exterior of house, Undated; 179; Sepia Print
    different angle than no. 178
  - Chi Psi Lodge - exterior, Undated; 180; Sepia Print
    Imprint: Stanford Bookstore
  - Delta Chi--exterior of house, Undated; 181; Sepia Print
  - Delta Tau Delta--exterior; side view, Undated; 182; Photo
    Caption: Delta Tau Delta
    R.&C.
  - Delta Tau Delta--exterior; front view, Undated; 183; Sepia Print
    Imprint: Hyde's Bookstore
  - Delta Upsilon--exterior, Undated; 184; Photo
    Caption: Delta Upsilon
    R&C
  - Gamma Phi Beta--exterior, Undated; 185; Sepia Print
  - Gamma Phi Beta--exterior, Undated; 186; Photo
    Caption: Gamma Phi Beta
  - Gamma Phi Beta--exterior, Undated; 187; Photo
  - Phi Delta Theta--exterior, Undated; 188; Photo
    Caption: Phi Delta Theta
  - Phi Delta Theta--exterior, Undated; 189; B/W Print
    print smaller than card (has white border)
    "Phi Delt" penciled in upside down on card back
  - Phi Kappa Psi--exterior, Undated; 190; Photo
    Caption: R.& C.
    Phi Kappa Psi
  - Phi Kappa Psi: brothers posing in front of house, Undated; 191; Photo
  - Phi Kappa Psi: brothers posing on house stairs, Undated; 192; Photo
  - Pi Beta Phi--exterior, Undated; 193; Photo
    Caption: Pi Beta Phi
    Message: Pi Phi
    Guthrie
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon--exterior, Undated; 194; Photo
    Caption: Sigma Alpha Epsilon
    print smaller than card (has small white border)
  - Sigma Chi--exterior, Undated; 195; Sepia Print
  - Sigma Nu--exterior, Undated; 196; Sepia Print
  - (?) Fraternity house--interior: stairway; piano, Undated; 197; Photo
    Message: A Stanford University fraternity house on the campus.
    Top rt.: "Dr. Albert Shumate," "12-10-68" in pencil
  - Fraternity house--interior: billiards table, Undated; 198; Photo
    Message: A fraternity house at Stanford University, Cal.
    top left: "Dr Albert Shumate," "12-10-68"
  - Fraternity house--interior, Undated; 199; Photo
    Message: A fraternity house at Stanford University, California.
  - Fraternity house--interior, Undated; 200; Photo
    bottom rt: "Dr Albert Shumate," "12-10-68"
  - Fraternities: The Row, 201; Sepia Print
    Caption: Fraternity Houses, Stanford University, Cal. 1846
  - Fraternities: The Row, Undated; 202; Tinted Print
    Caption: 2171 - Fraternity Row, Stanford University, California.
    "504" pencilied in bottom rt.
  - Fraternities: The Row, 203; Sepia Print
    Caption: On the Row, Stanford University, Cal. 1842
    Message: Dear Amy-Just got your postal + sent you a message to come down but found that you have gone. Hope you have a nice trip--wish I was with you. Love from Ethan.
    Postmarked July 30, 1913
  - Fraternities: The Row, Undated; 204; B/W Print
  - Fraternities: The Row, Undated; 205; B/W Print
    Caption: Lausen Row, Stanford University, Cal.
    Message: Dear Friend--Just a line to hope that you are improving in strength each day. Were you able to get out to see any of the Admission Day festivities? I was so glad when it was over. Time flies so rapidly. Our ill folks are improving, and I sincerely hope you are. Much love, E.C.
    postmarked Sept. 20, 1910
  - Fraternities: The Row, 1905 (?); 206; Photo
    Message: Row - Lausen 1905 (?)
    Mrs. Ramsey's house facing down Row. Alpha delt house next.-May 1941
    postmarked May 14, 1941
    image printed smaller than card; aligned top left
  - Frenchman's Tower, Undated; 207; Sepia Print
    Frenchman's Tower and Lake
  - Frenchman's Tower, Undated; 208; Sepia Print
  - Frenchman's Lake, Undated; 209; Photo
    Imprint: none
    back covered in black tagboard.
  - Frenchman's Lake, Undated; 210; Photo
    "Frenchman's Lake. Brasch 9/28/56". film negative available
  - Frost Memorial Ampitheatre, Undated; 211; Tinted Print
    Caption: Laurence Frost Memorial Ampitheatre, Stanford University, Palo Alto, California
    Imprint: Stanley A. Piltz Company
    Back caption: "Each Sunday afternoon under the direction of the University Chaplain, outdoor Vesper Services are held at this beautiful spot."
    Frost Memorial Ampitheatre
  - Gold Spike, Undated; 212; Color Print
    Imprint: H.S. Crocker Co.
    Back caption: "The Gold Spike: The spike commemorates the joining of the Central Pacific and Union Pacific Railways at Promontory, Utah, on May 10, 1869. Stanford University Museum of Art."
    Gold Spike.
  - Gymnasium: front view; pre-1906 earthquake, 1905; 213; Sepia Print
    Caption: Gymnasium Stanford University, Cal.
    Message: (Destroyed before occupancy, by the earthquake of 1906)
    Gym (1905)
  - Gymnasium: front view; pre-1906 earthquake, 1905; 214; Tinted Print
    Caption: 846 - Gymnasium, Stanford University, California
  - Gymnasium: angled view; pre-1906 earthquake, 1905; 215; B/W Print
    Caption: Gymnasium, Stanford University, California
    Message: Front: "This is our new gymnasium not yet completed. It will be up Satuirday Mar 9. [1906]"
    Imprint: Tupman Bros. by M. Reider
    postmarked June 19, 1905
  - Gymnasium: front view; pre-1906 earthquake, 1905; 216; Tinted Print
    Caption: Palo Alto, California, Leland Stanford jr. University Gymnasium.
  - Gymnasium and Library; after 1906 earthquake, 217; Photo
    Caption: Stanford Gymnasium & Library
  - Gymnasium: front view; after 1906 earthquake, 218; B/W Print
    Caption: Ruins at Gymnasium, Stanford University, after the earthquake, April 18, 1906
  - Gymnasium: front view; after 1906 earthquake, 219; Sepia Print
    Imprint: M. Reider
    Print is maroon-tinted.
  - Gymnasium: front view; after 1906 earthquake, 220; B/W Print
    Caption: The New Stanford University Gymnasium
    Totally wrecked by Earthquake, April 18th, 1906
    Imprint: O. Newman
  - Hoover House w/ inset photo of Hoover, Undated; 221; B/W Print
    Caption: The Hebert Hoover Home, Stanford University, At Palo Alto, California
    Imprint: Kenyon Photo
    hoover house
  - Herbert Hoover Home, 1944; 222; Color Print
    Imprint: Peninsula News Co.
  - Herbert Hoover Home, Undated; 223; B/W Print
    Caption: Home of Herbert Hoover, The Campus, Stanford University, California
  - Herbert Hoover Home, 1929; 224; Photo
    Caption: Herbert Hoover's Home, Stanford University
    Message: Dear Wilma, I am sending you a little birthday gift. I don't know whether you are at the same old place or not. Have not heard from you for weeks and weeks + more weeks. We have had a very pleasant summer the weather has been perfect. School started this a,m. so the children will be at the same old grind again. I'll tell the news when I answer your letter that I have not received yet. Love, Ida.
    Imprint: Shattuck Photo
  - Herbert Hoover Home w/ dog, Undated; 225; Photo
    Caption: Hoover's Home Palo Alto, CA
    x1.4 Herbert Hoover home on campus
  - Herbert Hoover Home--rear, pool, Undated; 226; Tinted Print
    Caption: Home and Swimming Pool of Herbert Hoover, The Campus, Stanford University, Calif. 6089
  - Herbert Hoover Home, Undated; 227; Tinted Print
    Caption: Home of President Hoover, The Campus, Stanford University, Calif.
  - Herbert Hoover Home, 228; Tinted Print
    Caption: President Herbert Hoover's Home on the Stanford University Campus
    Near Palo Alto in the Santa Clara Valley, California
    Imprint: Lofgren News Agency
  - Herbert Hoover Home, Undated; 229; Tinted Print
    Caption: Home of Former President Herbert Hoover, on the Stanford University Campus, Palo Alto, Calif.
    Imprint: Stanley A. Piltz
  - Herbert Hoover Home, 230; Tinted Print
    Caption: 32 Home of Herbert C. Hoover, Stanford University, California
    Imprint: Hyde's Book Storej
  - Hoover Tower, Undated; 231; B/W Print
    Caption: Stanford University, Palo Alto, Calif.
    Imprint: Mastercraft Pictures
    Hoover Tower
  - Hoover Tower, Undated; 232; B/W Print
    Imprint: Bardell Hi-Gloss Print.
  - Hoover Tower, Undated; 233; Color Print
    Imprint: West in Color
  - Hoover Tower, 234; Color Print
    Caption: Hoover Tower
    Imprint: R. & C. Hackanson
  - Hoover Tower, deep blue sky, Undated; 235; Color Print
    Imprint: Paulson News Agency
  - Hoover Tower, grey-blue sky, 236; Color Print
    Imprint: Mike Roberts Studio
  - Hoover Tower, 237; Tinted Print
    Caption: P.A.II:--Hoover Library on War, Revolution and Peace
    Stanford University, Palo Alto, Calif.
    Imprint: Scenic View Card Co.
    Post-it Note: "Postcard, Chap 3, Archives"
  - Hoover Tower, 1978; 238; Color Print
    Imprint: Impact, Inc.
  - Hopkins Marine Station, 1931 (?); 239; Photo
    Caption: Hopkins Marine Station, Pacific Grove, Calif.
    11683
    "Stanford Illustrated Review: June 1931, 780"
    Hopkins Marine Station
  - Hopkins Marine Station, 1931 (?); 240; Photo
    11684
    "Stanford Illustrated Review: June 1931, 779"
  - Japanese Clubhouse, Undated; 241; Photo
    Caption: Japanese Club
    Japanese Clubhouse
  - President's House, Undated; 242; Tinted Print
    Caption: President's House, Stanford University, CA
    Knoll
  - President's House, Undated; 243; B/W Print
  - Lagunita Court, Undated; 244; Photo
    Caption: Lagunita Court, Stanford Univ.
    Lagunita Court
  - Lake Lagunita, Undated; 245; B/W Print
    Lake Lagunita
  - Path by Lake Lagunita, sent 1910; 246; B/W Print
    Message: This is Saturday and just a week ago we started on our walking trip which we certainly enjoyed. My sister didn't come that other Sunday but is coming down to-morrow, so Bil and I shall conduct anothe sight seeing expedition around Stanford. We had a fine boat ride on the Lake yesterday--one of the girls who can row took us out. Will you be at home next Saturday and could I come to see you then? The week after is our vacation and BIl and I are going to the City. Hazel
  - Path by Lake Lagunita, Undated; 247; Sepia Print
  - Path by Lake Lagunita, Undated; 248; B/W Print
  - Path by Lake Lagunita, Undated; 249; Sepia Print
  - Path by Lake Lagunita, Undated; 250; Sepia Print
  - Sailboat on Lake Lagunita, Undated; 251; Sepia Print
  - Trees; Lake Lagunita, Undated; 252; B/W Print
    Caption: The Pines, Lagunita, Stanford University, Cal
    Message: Glad to hear all the good news. Tell Grace a letter is coming--next mail I hope. It is partly written now. Muriel is dressmaker again. C. at work these two days. Weather cooler. Glad you get the Republican. Muting seems to promise well, from telephone messages. Hope you are all better sleepers now. Love from all, Mary.
  - Lake Lagunita, Undated; 253; Sepia Print
  - Lake Lagunita, sent 1907; 254; B/W Print
    Caption: Lagunita, Stanford University, Cal.
    Message: Hoping you had a pleasant journey and are looking forward to even pleasanter prospects in your work. W.
  - Lake Lagunita, Undated; 255; Sepia Print
  - Lake Lagunita with Boat and TOwer, Undated; 256; B/W Print
    Caption: Lagunita, Stanford.
  - Lake Lagunita with Boat and Tower, Undated; 257; Photo
    Caption: Lagunita Lake--Stanford University, Cal.
    Imprint: Western Card Company
  - Canoes on Shore of Lake Lagunita, Undated; 258; Sepia Print
  - Lake Lagunita, Undated; 259; Photo
  - Lake Lagunita with Boat and Tower, 1916; 260; Tinted Print
    Caption: 1916--Lagunita, Stanford University, California.
    Imprint: Souvenir Publishing Co.
  - Rowers on Lake Lagunita, Undated; 261; B/W Print
  - Lake Lagunita, Undated; 262; B/W Print
  - Boat House by Lake Lagunita, Undated; 263; Photo
  - People by Lake Lagunita, Undated; 264; Sepia Print
  - People on Raft on Lake Lagunita, Undated; 265; B/W Print
  - Boat House on Lake Lagunita, Undated; 266; Sepia Print
  - Painting: People in a City, Undated; 267; Color Print
    Caption: Decoration for Lane Medical Library painted by Arthur F. Mathews
    Imprint: Furniture Shop
    Lane Medical Library
  - Painting of Workers in a Field, Undated; 268; Color Print
    Caption: Decoration for Lane Medical Library
  - Interior of Library (Reading Desk), 4/14/2013; 269; Sepia Print
    Message: New to-day. April 14, 1913.
    Thomas Welton Stanford Library
  - Exterior of Library, 1910; 270; B/W Print
    Caption: 1910--Library Building, Stanford University, California.
  - University Library, circa 1905; 271; Tinted Print
    Caption: Palo Alto, California, Leland Stanford jr. University Library
    Library (1905)
  - University Library, circa 1905; 272; Tinted Print
    Caption: Library, Stanford University, California.
    Imprint: Edward H. Mitchell, Publisher.
  - University Library, circa 1905; 273; B/W Print
    Caption: New Library, Stanford University
    Imprint: K.W. Simkins, Publisher
  - Library Under Construction, 1906; 274; Sepia Print
    Caption: Miss Hadden
    Message: Place card for a luncheon given by the Stanford Librarian for noted East Coast Librarians just before the 1906 earthquake
  - University Library, After Earthquake, 1906; 275; Tinted Print
    Caption: Stanford University Library, San Francisco, Calif.
    Message: Hello! Mother this was ruined in the earthquake. I saw this building a year ago when I was there. Mother you do not owe me any thing for these cards and any rime you want some just ask me and I will send them to you + (-?- -?-) Billy.
    Imprint: H.G. Zimmerman and Co.
  - University Library, After Earthquake, 1906; 276; Tinted Print
    Caption: Ruins of Stanford University Library
    Imprint: Boston Sunday American
  - University Library, After Earthquake, 1906; 277; B/W Print
    Caption: Library Building, Stanford University, after the Earthquake, April 19th 1906
  - University Library, After Earthquake, 1906; 278; B/W Print
    Caption: The Museum, Stanford University, after the earthquake, April 18, 1906
    ---Really the library
    Imprint: M. Rieder, Publisher
  - University Library, After Earthquake, 1906; 279; Tinted Print
    Caption: The Library Building, Stanford University, Palo Alto, Cal
    Wrecked by the earthquake of April 18, 1906
    Imprint: Rieder Cardinell Co.
  - University Library, After Earthquake, 1907; 280; B/W Print
    Caption: Stanford University Library.
    Message: (FRONT) This shows the ruins of the library--The city appears pretty badly shaken up even yet. (BACK) Sept. 12, '07. We are now on board the steamer "Hong Knog Maru" ready to start in about an hour. Had fine trip across continent. Nice day today. Love to all. Harriet & Willis.
    Imprint: H.G. Zimmerman & Co., Chicago
  - University Library, After Earthquake, 1912; 281; B/W Print
    Caption: Library, After the Earthquake, Palo Alto, Calif.
    Message: Aug. 4, 1912, Palo Alto. Just spent a few hours here--Peru(?) is awful--temperature about 150 in the shade I think--Love, (--cut off--)
  - University Library, After Earthquake, circa 1906; 282; B/W Print
    Caption: Ruins of the Library Building, Stanford University, Palo Alto, Cal., after the earthquake.
    Imprint: M. Rieder, pub.
  - View of Demolished Library Dome from Quad, circa 1913; 283; Sepia Print
    Message: June 18, 1913: The day we took Nellie Reed to visit Stanford.
    Imprint: RObinson & Crandall
  - University Library, Before and After Shots, Undated; 284; B/W Print
    Caption: Before and after
  - Library, Exterior, Undated; 285; Tinted Print
    Caption: Library, Stanford University, Palo Alto, California
    Imprint: Scenic VIew Card Co.
    Library (1919)
  - Library, Exterior, 1919; 286; B/W Print
  - Library, Exterior, Undated; 287; B/W Print
    Imprint: Bardell Hi-Gloss Print
  - Library, Exterior, Undated; 288; Tinted Print
  - Library, Exterior, Undated; 289; Tinted Print
    Caption: The Library, Stanford University, California
  - Library, Exterior, Undated; 290; B/W Print
  - Library and Hoover Tower, Undated; 291; Color Print
  - Library, Exterior Viewed from Quad, Undated; 292; Tinted Print
  - Library, Interior, Reading Room, Undated; 293; Photo
    Caption: Main Reading Room Stanford Uninversity Library
  - Library, Exterior, Undated; 294; B/W Print
    Caption: Library, Stanford University, Cal.
  - Mariposa House, Undated; 295; Photo
    Caption: Mariposa
    Imprint: Manteista
    Mariposa House
  - Mausoleum, Undated; 296; B/W Print
    Caption: Mausoleum--Stanford
    Mausoleum
  - Mausoleum, Undated; 297; Tinted Print
  - Mausoleum, Undated; 298; B/W Print
  - Mausoleum, 299; Sepia Print
    Caption: The Stanford Mausoleum, Palo Alto, Cal. 1848
  - Mausoleum, Undated; 300; B/W Print
  - Mausoleum, 1902; 302; Sepia Print
    Caption: 1902--The Stanford Mausoleum, Stanford University, California
    Message: June 26th, 1923
  - Mausoleum, Undated; 303; Tinted Print
    Caption: Mausoleum, Stanford University, California
  - Mausoleum, 1/10/1908; 304; Tinted Print
    Caption: The Mausoleum, Stanford University, California
    Message: Harry Jan 10 '08
  - Mausoleum, Undated; 305; Tinted Print
  - Mausoleum, Undated; 306; Tinted Print
  - Mausoleum, Undated; 307; Tinted Print
  - Mausoleum, Undated; 308; B/W Print
    Caption: Mausoleum, Stanford University, Cal.